

DETAILS

Address:

Krakow

Phone:

+48 503 129 296

Email:

igor.batko.batko@gmail.com

Date of birth: 23.05.1998

SKILLS

•••• Communication

•••• Working in team

•••• Working under pressure

•••• Coding

•••• Adapting and fast learning

IGOR BATKO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

24 year old man born in Krakow. Witty and ambitious water and winter sports enthusiast. Windsurfing instructor since 2016 and head-instructor for last 2 years. Interested in computers since a child. Began programming few years ago as a hobby and started a front-end bootcamp in September 2021.

Main technologies i worked with:

- -HTML5
- -CSS/SCSS
- -JAVASCRIPT
- -REACT
- -GIT

I am highly open-minded and love to meet new opportunities. I can assure you that I will try my best to bring some value & positive atmosphere to your team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Windsurfing instructor at FunSurf

Jun. 2016 - Sep. 2019

Chalupy

Windsurfing head-instructor at FunSurf

Jun. 2020 - Present

• Chalupy

Swimming freelance-instructor

Sep. 2019 - Present

various places

Skiing freelance-instructor

Jan. 2015. - Present

• various places

Customer Advisor in ski shop - Adventure Sports

Dec. 2020 - Jun. 2021

Krakow

Math teacher in project - Wirtualny Nauczyciel

Jan. 2021 - Jun. 2021

• remote

EDUCATION

VIII LO in Krakow

Jan 2014 - 2017

Windsurfing instructor course and practice

May 2016 - Jun. 2016

Ski PZN instructor

Dec. 2014

Kodilla Front-end React Developer course

Sep 2021- March 2022

LANGUAGES

Polish: Native

English: B2